ABDUL FAHMI AZIZ

PERUMAHAN BOGOR RAYA PERMAI BLOK FA 08, WEST JAVA

abdulfahmi78@gmail.com 087770173111

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a final year student at the University of Ibn Khaldun Bogor majoring in Informatics Engineering. I have experience as a back end web developer with javascript language especially Node JS on several projects and also a graduate of Bangkit Academy 2022 with learning path cloud computing using GCP.

WORK EXPERIENCE

University Ibn Khaldun Bogor | Computer Lab Assistant

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

- Become one of the practicum assistants in the numerical method course, processing basic mathematics with MATLAB applications such as systems of linear and non-linear equations, taylor series and others.
- Management of student learning time in practicum.

K3I Korlantas – IT Support

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

- Help work on several back end web features with express js such as Trip on (For monitoring member trip) and other.
- Fixed some application bugs.
- Managing K3I application data for development with dbeaver.
- Make a documentation testing with Insomnia.
- Use Postgree SQL for database
- Make a user guide with mircrosoft word.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technical Information, University Ibn Khaldun Bogor

September 2019 – Present

Current IPK 3,86

Bangkit Academy 2022 | Cloud Computing

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Learn the fundamentals of cloud computing to deploy applications, monitor operations, and manage enterprise solutions with these specializations:

- Web, API, & Back-end Basic
- Google IT Support
- Google Cloud Computing Foundations
- Google Cloud Engineer Learning Path
- Google Cloud Skillboost

ADDITIONAL SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Finalist Edsen Hackathon 2022 (Issued by "Badepay" Payment Using Student Card & Facial Recognition)
- Awarde Pancakarsa Scholarship Kabupaten Bogor (Juli 2021 Present)
- Create a website with wordpress and manage cpanel on the SMPN 2 Kemang website, Bogor Regency
- Parcitipant of International Carnival on High Impact Educational Practices in Islamic Studies 2022 (ICHIEPIS2022)

ORGANIZATION

- Leader Of OSIS MA Al Riyadl (2018-2019)
- Deputy Secretary Yayasan Pondok Pesantren Putra Al-Riyadl (2017-2018)